[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Princess Fiona transformed into every night as a result of a curse in the 2001 movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "A monster", "incorrect_answers": ["A frog", "A werewolf", "A firefly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nephrectomy is a surgical removal of which internal organ?", "correct_answer": "Kidney", "incorrect_answers": ["Thyroid gland", "Pancreas", "Spleen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plan B.  Lets just kill each other. is a quote from what movie directed by John Woo?", "correct_answer": "Face/Off", "incorrect_answers": ["Mission Impossible", "Constantine", "The Man in the Iron Mask"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the digestive tract of rabbits?", "correct_answer": "They are hindgut digesters.", "incorrect_answers": ["Their cecum, together with the large intestine, comprises about 25-30% of rabbits digestive tract.", "All of these", "Their cecum is about 5 times bigger than their stomach."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The alcohol content is very high in absinthe. It can be as high as this %.", "correct_answer": "85 %", "incorrect_answers": ["75 %", "65 %", "95 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these islands is known as the location of numerous important world observatories?", "correct_answer": "Hawaii", "incorrect_answers": ["Okinawa", "Cyprus", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why shouldnt blackberries be picked after September 29 according to a popular superstition in the United Kingdom?", "correct_answer": "They belong to the devil from this day on.", "incorrect_answers": ["A woman who consumes them after this date will never get pregnant.", "All of these", "The one who eats them will grow hairs on their back."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Point Break, in preparation for a raid on the house of the suspected bank robbers, Gary Busey pretends he is looking for a lost dog. What name does he use for the dog?", "correct_answer": "Scooby", "incorrect_answers": ["Pluto", "Toto", "Astro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first Assistant District Attorney on Law and Order?", "correct_answer": "Paul Robinette", "incorrect_answers": ["Benjamin Stone", "Bill Flynn", "Michael Moriarty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Point Break, FBI agent Utah was quarterback for a major college football team and ended up getting hurt in the Rose Bowl. What team did he play against in that bowl game?", "correct_answer": "USC", "incorrect_answers": ["Arizona", "Arizona State", "UCLA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although gravity has been a subject of much research and scientific work, the actual cause of gravitational forces remains unknown.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a one-piece garment, that men in some hot countries wear around their waist.", "correct_answer": "Loincloth", "incorrect_answers": ["Pantalettes", "Boxers", "Crinoline"]}]